{
    "6" : {
        "3.1" :  [
            {"Instructions" : "Unscramble the word",
            "Question" : "lyuj",
            "Answer": "July"},
            {"Instructions" : "Unscramble the word",
            "Question" : "ryanjua",
            "Answer": "January"},
            {"Instructions" : "Unscramble the word",
            "Question" : "arubeyfr",
            "Answer": "February"},
            {"Instructions" : "Unscramble the word",
            "Question" : "ralpi",
            "Answer": "April"},
            {"Instructions" : "Unscramble the word",
            "Question" : "arhmc",
            "Answer": "March"},
            {"Instructions" : "Unscramble the word",
            "Question" : "nrebovem",
            "Answer": "November"},
            {"Instructions" : "Unscramble the word",
            "Question" : "njue",
            "Answer": "June"},
            {"Instructions" : "Unscramble the word",
            "Question" : "ionap ctnecro",
            "Answer": "Piano Contest"},
            {"Instructions" : "Unscramble the word",
            "Question" : "dnaec stncote",
            "Answer": "Dance Contest"},
            {"Instructions" : "Unscramble the word",
            "Question" : "soloch takerm",
            "Answer": "School Market"},
            {"Instructions" : "Unscramble the word",
            "Question" : "rtocbeo",
            "Answer": "October"},
            {"Instructions" : "Unscramble the word",
            "Question" : "omeiv aetislfv",
            "Answer": "Movie Festival"},
            {"Instructions" : "Unscramble the word",
            "Question" : "dreebmce",
            "Answer": "December"},
            {"Instructions" : "Unscramble the word",
            "Question" : "aym",
            "Answer": "May"},
            {"Instructions" : "Unscramble the word",
            "Question" : "idelf pirt",
            "Answer": "Field Trip"},
            {"Instructions" : "Unscramble the word",
            "Question" : "atgsuu",
            "Answer": "August"},
            {"Instructions" : "Unscramble the word",
            "Question" : "srebtepem",
            "Answer": "September"},
            {"Instructions" : "Unscramble the word",
            "Question" : "srebtepem",
            "Answer": "September"}
        ]

    }
}